VINCE CHANG

7120 Shoreline Drive #2214, San Diego, CA 92122 Phone: (650) 274-2333 : Email: vincechangsf@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/vincechang26: Portfolio: https://vincehacks.github.io

OBJECTIVE

I am a UC San Diego new grad with a B.S in Computer Science. I am a unique problem solver who has work experience in leadership, teamwork, and is passionate about motivating others. As a Software Engineer, I would become a valuable asset by bringing innovated ideas and by developing clean deployable code.

EDUCATION

University of California, San Diego, CA, September 2014 - Present

- Computer Science, B.S March 2017 expected graduation
- Relevant Coursework:
 - Software Engineering
- · Design & Analysis of Algorithms
- Advanced Data Structures
- Operating Systems

WORK EXPERIENCE

Instructional Assistant, UCSD, San Diego, CA, Sept 2016 - Dec 2016 Usability and Information Architecture

- Designed curriculum that emphasized on user interaction, research, and prototyping with design tools such as Axure, Balsamig, & Photoshop
- Assisted students with building web portfolios in HTML, CSS, JavaScript through Bootstrap Framework.

Software Engineering Intern, DIRECTV, El Segundo, CA, June 2016 - Sept 2016

- Performed system level functional software testing for NFL Sunday Ticket on iOS and Android platforms
- Learned the Django Platform to manage application versions
- Measured system performance and stress-tested servers using JMeter
- Updated tasks and requirements during SCRUM

<u>Computer Science Tutor, UCSD, San Diego, CA, March 2015 - June 2016</u> Software Engineering; Intro to Computer Science: Java; Software Tools Lab

- Assisted students with understanding software development and agile methods, including design, implementation, testing & debugging
- Monitored lab hours that focused on: Unix, GIT, Python, debugging, Object-Oriented Programming

PROJECTS

Shake-Kryptic (WIP)

Web/mobile app that allows users to generate a unique handshake with others. Currently still in design phase with wireframes and mockups. Plan on using MYSQL as database and model after MVC pattern to handle the backend.

Synth

Mobile Music App that has been redesigned through strategically conducted case studies. We evaluated the daily music user's likes/dislikes on Spotify, Pandora, Soundcloud, and Google Play. After analyzing and weighing pros and cons, my team is proud to announce the birth of Synth.

Dancify (SD HACK-A-THON)

Web app that connects you with other people who would like to attend a dance event. Users are matched based on their profile information which include availability, location, gender

TECH SKILLS

- · Agile Methods
- OO Design
- Android
- · Hack-a-Thon
- Debugging
- Github
- MVC
- Django
- UML Diagrams
- SCRUM

LANGUAGES

- Java
- C++
- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- Python (WIP)
- Ruby (WIP)

IDE's

- Android Studio
- Eclipse
- IntelliJ